macworldiworld.com 2015-05-19

# Macworld / iWorld 2014 – Privacy Policy

This is a Web site of IDG World Expo Corp.

IDG World Expo Corp.  
3 Speen Street, Suite 320  
Framingham, MA 01701  
We can be reached via e-mail at [idgworldexpo@idgworldexpo.com](mailto:idgworldexpo@idgworldexpo.com) or you can reach us by telephone at (508) 879-6700.

**Information Collected**

IDG World Expo collects personally identifying information and data about individuals, their company, and their company’s demographics (personally identifying information and data) including (i) when you provide information to IDG World Expo, such as when you register or sign up for any of our products such as, but not limited to, events, conferences, on-line seminars contests, RSS Feeds, content delivery via sms text or other technologies, webcasts, contest, sweepstakes, and other communications with IDG World Expo; (ii) when you register or sign up on any IDG World Expo site, your information will be known to IDG World Expo; and (iii) from time to time we may add other information that we collect from third party sources to enhance the information that you provided to IDG World Expo.

**Notice of New Policy Changes**

Below is the current policy regarding the usage of personally identifying information and data collected by IDG World Expo. We reevaluate this policy on an ongoing basis. IDG World Expo reserves the right to change its privacy policy. However, if there are any changes to the use of personally identifying information and data that is different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify you by posting a notice on our Web site.

**Cookies**

IDG World Expo, or one of our IDG affiliated companies, or third party partners may place an online tracking technology such as a “cookie” in the browser files of a user’s computer. The cookie itself does not contain any personally identifying information, except when such information has been supplied by a user.  In addition, cookies placed in the browser files of a user’s computer by a third party advertiser, may be used by the advertiser to collect web viewing data to serve further online interest-based advertising, also known as online behavioral advertising.

If you have visited our Web site, the information in your “cookie” is used to provide a more personalized experience on the Web site. This cookie identifies you as a unique user by means of a tracking ID. However, we cannot link that user ID with personal identifying information and data about you such as your name or e-mail address.

Other cookies without personally identifying information and data are used to enable IDG World Expo to manage the banner advertisements presented or personalized information to the user.

Browsers or third-party software can allow you to block the use of cookies while you surf our site. Or, you can use third-party “anonymizer” services to mask information in your cookies, or even general data such as your IP address. In such cases, you would not be able to take advantage of most of the personalization services offered by IDG World Expo website(s).

The aggregated information we collect may be used for a number of purposes including the following: 1. to improve the content and design of the IDG World Expo Web site. 2. to enable an audit bureau to verify our claims of traffic to the site 3. to help advertisers, potential advertiser, exhibitors, potential exhibitors, sponsors, potential sponsors, or marketers to assess the suitability of the site for their ad campaigns 4. we may create and use aggregate customer data to understand more about the interests of our customers and may use the data to offer goods and services we believe may be of interest to our customers, on behalf of IDG World Expo, its sister IDG companies, or selection organizations.

**Postal Addresses**

Postal addresses, and other personally identifying information and data may be used to promote IDG World Expo and other IDG companies’ products and services, and may be rented and/or licensed to selected outside firms for promotional purposes. Offers for which the personally identifying information and data are rented and/or licensed for use and the users are required to target their offers carefully.

**Residential and Business Telephone Numbers & Telemarketing**

Residential and business telephone numbers provided to IDG World Expo may be used by IDG World Expo, IDG, and other IDG companies, affiliates and its advertisers for promotional purposes. IDG World Expo may rent and/or license for use phone numbers to selected outside firms for promotional purposes. Offers for which the numbers are rented and/or licensed for use are required to target their offers carefully.

**Mobile Telephone Numbers**

Mobile telephone numbers that are provided to IDG World Expo may be used to provide the products and services you’ve specifically requested, such as, but not limited to content delivery via sms text or other technologies, and for customer service related to the products and services you’ve requested. With your express consent, your mobile telephone number may be used to promote other products and services of IDG World Expo, as well as the products and services of other IDG companies. Further, your mobile telephone number may, with your express consent, be used to promote the products and services of carefully chosen third parties. At any time, you may “opt-out” of receiving communications via your mobile phone from IDG World Expo, other IDG companies, and third parties by sending an e-mail to [idgworldexpo@idgworldexpo.com](mailto:idgworldexpo@idgworldexpo.com). Because many phone companies recycle phone numbers, it is possible for users who purchase a new phone to receive messages that the previous owner had subscribed to or otherwise consented to receive.

**Fax Numbers**

Fax numbers provided to IDG World Expo may be used to communicate information about an IDG World Expo event to an attendee, exhibitor, speaker, and/or sponsor. Information communicated may include, but is not limited to, confirmation of registration for an attendee, receipt of conference fee for an attendee, exhibitor or sponsors newsletter to an exhibitor, speaker, or sponsor, welcome letter to an exhibitor, speaker, or sponsor, list of due dates to an exhibitor, speaker, or sponsor, and general information regarding an event.  Except as set forth in this policy no fax numbers are rented and/or licensed to outside firms.

**E-mail Addresses**

E-mail addresses provided to IDG World Expo may be used to collect feedback, promote IDG World Expo and IDG products and services, and they may be rented to other firms and/or licensed for promotional purposes. When you provide your e-mail address to us, you agree to receive e-mail from outside firms, IDG World Expo, its sister IDG companies, and the IDG Network. We allow users to “opt-out” of receiving e-mail from outside firms when e-mail information is collected and with each e-mail use of the user’s address you can individually “opt-out” of receiving further e-mail from outside firms, IDG World Expo (or a specific IDG World Expo event), and its sister IDG companies that sent you the e-mail. If a user does not choose to “opt-out” at the time the e-mail address is collected, or does not respond to the questions concerning how we may use their e-mail address, the address may be used by IDG World Expo, its sister IDG Companies, or rented and/or licensed for use to outside firms. Offers for which the e-mail address is rented and/or licensed for use require the users to target their offers carefully. Users who want to “opt-out” of receiving any e-mail, or want to otherwise change their preferences may do so by sending an e-mail to [idgworldexpo@idgworldexpo.com](mailto:idgworldexpo@idgworldexpo.com).

**Transfer of Ownership**

In the event that the ownership of this Web site, IDG World Expo’s assets, and/or any of its products are sold or transferred, all lists and data which contain personally identifying information and data including for example user name, address, company name, telephone number, demographic information, buying information, other data and e-mail address, will be transferred to the new owner.

**Use or Disclosure of Personally Identifying Information**

We may use or disclose personally identifying information if we have a good-faith belief that the disclosure is reasonably necessary (a) to satisfy applicable law, regulation, legal process, or enforceable governmental request, (b) to enforce agreements we have with you, (c) to address fraud or security issues, or (d) to protect against harm to the rights, property, or safety of IDG World Expo, or our employees or customers.

**IDG PUBLISHING NETWORK ONLINE REGISTRATION PRIVACY POLICY**

Below is the current policy regarding the usage of personally identifying information and data collected by the IDG Publishing Network.  We reevaluate this policy on an ongoing basis based on feedback from readers.  The IDG Publishing Network reserves the right to change its privacy policy.  However, if there are any changes to the use of personally identifiable information and data that is different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify you by posting a notice on our website.

**About the IDG Publishing Network**

The International Data Group, Inc. (IDG) family of on-line and print publications consists of hundreds of award-winning titles including CIO, CSO, InfoWorld, Computerworld, Network World, Macworld and PC World.  The IDG Publishing Network is a growing collection of IDG web sites that presently includes cio.com, csoonline.com, computerworld.com, infoworld.com, networkworld.com, macworld.com, and pcworld.com.  A complete listing is available at [www.idg.com](http://www.idg.com/).

To access restricted content on any IDG Publishing Network web site you must be a member of the IDG Publishing Network.  To become a member of the IDG Publishing Network, you need to provide certain information about yourself.  Any of the IDG Publishing Network sites may use this identifying information for internal analytical and business development purposes and, to send you email.  However, other forms of communication, including postal mail, may be directed to you pursuant to the site’s specific privacy policy, as may be updated from time to time.

You can “opt-out” of receiving further email by clicking the appropriate links that appear at the bottom of any email you receive. If you do not want to receive other types of communication, including as applicable, postal mail, from the editor and publisher of the site, please refer to the site’s privacy policy for the procedure to follow.

The IDG Publishing Network is intended for individuals over the age of 13 years old.  Personal information may not be provided by anyone under 13 years of age.  Further no one under 13 years old may participate in the forums or chat rooms or any other areas where public discussions may take place.  In addition no one under that age of 18 may conduct any transactions for the purposes or purchasing or selling any items.  Parents should be sure that their children are not conducting any of the above activities on the IDG Publishing Network.

If you have any questions or comments regarding the IDG Publishing Network or its use of information please send email to postmasterhelp@idgcommunications.com or write to us at:

**IDG Communications, Inc.** **Customer Service,  
TSG Department 5 Speen St.,  
Framingham MA 01701 USA**

**Last updated: February 26, 2014**
